傲骨之战
第一季 第六集
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译      Alex  Margaery  吃冰棒  dzysteven
翻译      capitaljack  一点都不酷喵  胡说大王
校对      free·不是直男·维塔  某羽
时间轴      Avis
后期      你是不是饿得慌
总监      free·是小仙女·维塔
最新海外影视剧下载
总而言之
Basically,
有些人做事能力就是比其他人强
some people are just better at things than others.
编码就是这个道理
That's what coding makes you realize.
七就是七
The number seven is the number seven.
不是你说它是八
If you call it the number eight,
它就真的能变成八
you don't actually make it the number eight,
你只是在让自己难堪
you just embarrass yourself.
同样道理  男性在创造力上优于女性
Likewise, men are better at invention than women.
这是事实
Just a fact.
如今  这惹到了社交正义战士
Now, this makes SJWs upset.
他们觉得这个事实有些问题
They think there's something wrong with the fact
社交正义战士：进步派的俚语表达
他们想改变这点
and they want to change it,
但是谷歌一下
but go to a Google search
输入"女性发明"
and type in "She invents"
它会提示说"你是指男性发明吗"
and it'll ask, "Did you mean he invents?"
或者是说一年前才能搜索到
Or it did until a year ago.
你想知道为什么会有另类右翼吗
You want to know why there's an alt-right?
反对主流政治  通过网媒故意散布有争议内容  持有极端保守或反对变革观点的意识形态组织
因为谷歌直接改了算法
Because Google just changed its algorithm
这样那些酷客才不会被男性发明而
so the cucks wouldn't be offended that men invent
酷客：团结友爱的保守党  属于另类右翼用语
女性对社会基本没贡献的言论冒犯到...
and women barely contribute to soci...
那只是由我的版主指出的问题贴之一
That's just one posting flagged as problematic by my moderators.
这里还有...
Here are...
4758份帖子
4,758 more.
这也是我今天召集你们的原因
That's why I called you here today.
同时我也想看看
Oh, and also I wanted to see
我的新中西部律所是什么样的
what my new Midwest law firm looked like.
欢迎您大驾光临  格罗斯先生
We're glad to have you here, Mr. Gross.
谢谢  戴安
Thanks, Diane.
不像我那些有许多白人面孔的律所
Not quite as many white faces as at my other law firms.
我给大家带了份见面礼
Um, I have a little gift for you guys.
就是它
Here you go.
瞧
Voilà.
雷迪克&博斯曼&科斯"塔"团队 「应为Kolstad」
把这些分给大家
Uh, pass those around both directions.
他把我名字写错了
He misspelled my name.
他一年能带来8600万收入
He's bringing in 86 million a year.
我会告诉他怎么写你的名字
I'll teach him how to spell your name.
以下是我的诉求
Here is what I need.
服务条款
A term of service.
我有两个网站快变成
I have two sites that have become like
种族主义和性别歧视横行的"西大荒"
the Wild West of racism and sexism.
指尚无法制的美国西部
我的社群网站服务「查查交友」和「瞎掰网」
My Facebook-like service Chummy Friends and, uh, Scabbit.
这有一个例子
And here's a sample from that.
"太棒了..."
"Great..."
黑人历史月到了
it's Black History Month.
赞颂黑人在美国历史发展中所扮演的重要角色
让这些"门前猴"更有借口
Gives all those porch monkeys an excuse
对非洲人及非裔美国人的贬低之意
比平常大吵大闹
to be more annoying than usual.
我知道这里有些让你们倍感不适的言论
I'm sure you'll be disgusted by what you find in here,
这不仅影响恶劣
but it's not just bad,
同时也有损我的生意
it's also hurting my business.
在线广告避而远之
It scares off online advertising.
所以  为了删除这些特定的信息
So, you want us to come up with a code
你想让我们制定一项条款
in order to delete certain posts?
没错  而且这些用户应该被封号
Yes, and which users should be banned.
听我说  戴安
Now, look, Diane,
不用担心美国公民自由联盟那边
this is not something I have to worry about with the ACLU.
我有这些服务的所有权
I own these services.
我觉得怎么合适怎么来
I can control them in any way I see fit.
我注意到他只关注戴安
I notice only eyes for Diane.
-没错  -我们得找她谈谈
- Mm-hmm. - We got to talk to her.
-确保他也是我们的当事人  -没错
- Make sure he's our client, too. - Mm.
现在有个坏消息摆在你们面前
And now here's the bad news for you.
迪士尼公司威胁要把它所有广告
Disney is threatening to pull
从我的网站上撤下来
all of its advertising from my sites,
所以今天下午五点我就要这个条款
so I need a TOS by 5:00 P.M. Today.
所以  应该没人要去厕所吧
So, I hope no one needs to use the bathroom.
还有一件事
You know what, one last thing.
我喜欢这所非裔美国人律所
I love that this firm is African-American.
我看着你们的脸...
I look at all your faces and...
我看到了希望
and I see hope.
那么  我们应该先分一下组
So, we should probably split up into groups.
别  先把信息分下类
No, let's divide up the posts.
好  每人拿一摞
Agreed. Everybody take a pile.
种族歧视的信息放这里
Uh, let's have racist posts here,
反犹主义的帖子放这里  剩下恐吓的信息
anti-Semitic right here, and at the end up there
全都放那里
we'll have threatening posts.
我们得再分一类
Uh, we might need another pile.
什么
What?
"我想你..."
"I would love to see you...
死  不是因为你是女权主义者
dead. Not because you're a feminist,
而是因为你就是个大婊子
but because you're an enormous fucking bitch.
厌女主义的信息放这里
Misogynistic posts here.
好了  开工吧
All righty. Let's get to it.
我的天
Oh, good God.
这个信息不堪入目...
This one is disgusting...
爸  我最近工作很忙  但是  我尽量吧
Dad, I've been working pretty hard lately, but, um, I'll try.
我得挂了
I have to go.
已经过去两周了
Well, it's just been two weeks.
我不知道还能保释多长时间
I don't know how long I'll be out on bail.
可问题是  我现在是一名律师
But the problem is, i'm an associate.
我自己也身不由己
I don't control my own fate.
今晚过来吧  我给你泡爱尔兰咖啡
Come by tonight. I'll make Irish coffees.
好  我去
Okay. I will.
我真得挂了  戴安在叫我
I really have to go now. Diane is calling me.
今晚见
See you tonight.
"而且还要把你剁了  然后做..."
"...and chop you up, too, and do the s..."
等等  停一下  把整条信息再读一遍
Wait, stop. Read the whole thing again.
再读下那个
Read-Read that again.
好  "你真是个伪君子"
Okay. "You're such a hypocrite."
你把宝宝的器官剁了扔到垃圾箱
You chop up baby parts and drop them in dumpsters.
你怎么知道我们不会把你也剁了
Why don't you think we wouldn't chop you up, too,
如法炮制
and do the same?
这个事关政治  是与政见相关的信息
It's politics. It's a political point of view.
不  这是恐吓
No, it's a threat.
他暗示说他会剁了那个人
He suggests he'll chop up the respondent.
不  他是说为什么他不该把她剁了呢
No, he's saying why shouldn't he chop her up?
-他意在指出虚伪行为  -你在开玩笑吗
- He's pointing out the hypocrisy. - Seriously?
他显然是在恐吓
He clearly means it as intimidating.
这是两个人之间平等交流各自政见
It's the equivalent of me taking your political thinking
从而得出合乎逻辑的结论
to its logical conclusion.
如果你不把未出世的宝宝当人看
If you don't treat an unborn baby as human,
那我们为什么要把你当人看呢
then why don't we not treat you as human?
好吧  我们还是投票表决吧
Okay, why don't we vote on this?
什么  你是普通律师  而我是合伙人
Excuse me. You're an associate. I'm the partner.
拜托  朱利叶斯
come on, Julius.
等等  我们折中一下
Okay, wait, wait. Let's compromise.
没必要按质排辈
There's no reason to call rank.
卢卡  把政见的归一类
Lucca, start a political pile.
我们稍后再做决定
We'll-We'll decide on it later.
那我们该给这一条投个票吗
Then should we vote on this one?
这属于恐吓吗
Is this a threat?
-"有一个..."  -思维实验
- "Here's a... - ...thought experiment.
如果「人类清除计划」成真  你打算强奸谁
If The Purge were real, who would you set out to rape?
惊悚电影  讲述为减少人类数量  美国政府展开一个12小时内允许所有犯罪行为的计划
我的话  就选赞达亚
For me, it'd be Zendaya.
美国女演员  代表作「蜘蛛侠」
恐吓  绝对是恐吓
Threat. Clearly a threat.
等等
Wait a second.
他没有真的恐吓说要强奸她
He didn't actually threaten to rape her.
在我看来他只是在谈论电影罢了
It seems to me he's talking about a movie.
你真的要为这个做辩解吗
Are you seriously defending this?
不  我没有为其做辩解
No, I'm not defending this.
我是站在法律角度来判别恐吓
I'm making a legal distinction between a threat,
现实恐吓  和粗鄙的厌女评论的区别
a real threat, and a crude, misogynistic comment.
你的意思是这个人得说出"我想强奸你"吗
You're saying the person has to say, "I want to rape you"?
这个人必须说出"我要强奸你"
The person has to say, "I am going to rape you."
否则是受到言论自由保护的
Everything else is protected speech.
所以如果有人写"我想"而不是"我要"
So, we can't do anything about it
我们就无能为力了吗
if the person writes, "I want to" Instead of "I'm going to."
事实上  我们是能有所作为的
Actually, we can do anything we want.
格罗斯先生有这些网站的所有权
Mr. Gross owns these sites.
他制定任何条款都是合法的
He can legally set whatever terms he wants.
没错  但这些条款必须讲求公平
Yes, but the terms have to be fair.
好吧  这有条信息
Okay, so, here we go.
-"我想..."  -强奸你
- "I want to... - ...rape you.
我想去你家  然后强...
I want to come to your house and ra...
若不是身处这个时代  我要强奸到你血...
If this were another century, I could fuck you until you bl...
那些酷客可不会承认想强奸你
The cucks could never admit to wanting to rape you.
这些信息都是同一个人发的
These posts are all from the same person.
指向同一个人吗
Directed at the same person?
没错  十条关于强奸的信息
Yes. Ten posts about rape.
不该对那个人封号吗
So, shouldn't that person be banned?
这可不仅仅是恐吓
It's not just about threats.
这已经算频繁骚扰了
It's about continual harassment.
我们难道不是应该
Well, isn't the problem here
基于敏感性而不是内容本身
that we're thinking of censoring based on sensitivities
对这些信息进行审查吗
and not content?
那重要吗
Does that matter?
我认为重要
I think it does.
如果我一天被攻击50次呢
And if I'm attacked 50 times a day?
那我同情你
Then I sympathize with you,
但是我认为言论的好坏不应改由那些
but I don't think speech should be judged by those
认为自己最受伤害的人来评价
who feel the most harmed.
"我希望他们"
"I'm hoping they
找到你的地址
find your address.
我希望他们割掉你的乳头  在血泊中强奸你
I hope they cut off your nipples and rape you in a pool of blood.
这是发送到我账户的50条信息之一
This is one of 50 posts sent to my account.
但那是关于你父母的丑闻的  对吗
Uh, but that's about your parents' scandal, right?
我猜是的
My guess is yes,
但是有时候他们忙着讨论强奸我
but sometimes they're so busy discussing my rape
使得他们  没时间陈述他们的理由
that they, uh, they don't have time to state their reasoning.
我认为我们应该就屏蔽
I think we should vote on banning users
不断发送骚扰信息的用户进行投票
who continually send harassing posts.
那么我们的问题来了
Here's the problem for us.
你理解不断是什么意思
You know what continual means,
我理解不断是什么意思
I know what continual means,
但是我们如何定义它
how do we define it?
会有人挑措辞的破绽玩文字游戏的
There are people out there who will quibble.
是的  但格罗斯先生想让我们拿出一套制度
Yeah, but Mr. Gross wants us to come up with a code.
那是底线
That's the bottom line.
否则的话我们不过是整理文件而已
Otherwise, we're just filing papers.
喂  怎么了
Hey. What's up?
...今天见
...see you today.
什么  我听不清
What? I can't hear you.
今天午饭的时候我需要跟你见个面
I need to see you today at lunch.
你穿什么颜色的内裤呢
What color panties are you wearing?
我不知道  我是色盲
I don't know. I'm color blind.
辩诉交易会谈时我意识到
I was in a plea bargaining session when I realized
就因为我没滚床单
I sent someone to jail for 30 years
就害了一个人蹲30年大牢
because I hadn't gotten laid.
你想聊聊吗
You wanted to talk?
是的  我回头再找你说这事
Uh, y-yeah, i'll have to get back to you on that.
四小时之后
Four hours.
阁下  我就是不明白
Sir, I just don't understand
我们为什么要让嫌疑人保释
why we're undercutting our most important case
而削弱我们最重要的案子
by letting the suspect out on bail.
你看这盒沙拉
Look at this salad.
真的有什么好沙拉吗
Are there any actually good salads?
中国鸡肉沙拉
Chinese chicken salad?
上面的腰果和橙子都挺好
I mean, the cashews and oranges are good,
其余的不过是普通沙拉而已
but the rest is just salad.
阁下  这次谈话的重点在于
Sir, as important as this conversation is,
伊利诺伊州最可憎的人保释出狱
the most hated man in Illinois is out on bail.
你为何如此纠结克里斯特瓦做什么事情呢
Why are you so concerned about what Kresteva is doing?
因为我认为他正在给更重要的案子搞破坏
Because I think he's hurting more important cases.
他是想在警察暴力执法的案子上
He's trying to save Illinois money
给伊利诺伊州省点钱
on these police brutality cases.
所以  如果他拿雷迪克&博斯曼做了典型
So, if he makes Reddick/Boseman an example,
就能吓跑其他20家律所
he scares off 20 other firms.
如果他必须让亨利·林德尔保释出狱
If he has to let this Henry Rindell guy out on bail
来证明他的正确  那就随便他
to make his case, so be it.
好的  阁下
Yes, sir.
等等
Wait.
我能做的是
This is what I can do.
你刚刚被提拔为那什么小组工作负责人
You've just been made oversight head of...
算了  职名的事过会儿再说
whatever, we'll figure out the title later.
我想让你监督雷迪克&博斯曼的案子
I want you to supervise the Reddick/Boseman cases.
-啥  为什么  -因为执着
- What? Why? - Because you're obsessed.
我在利用你的执着
I'm harnessing your obsession.
把他们的进展汇报给我
Report back to me on their progress.
我有否决权吗
Will I have veto power?
没有  有监督权
No. Oversight power.
那是什么
What is that?
那就好比一架没有炸弹的无人机
It's like a drone without bombs.
为什么每次我升职
Why is it that whenever I get a promotion,
都感觉像降职似的
I feel like I'm being demoted?
问得好
It's a good question.
找到答案的时候记得告诉我
Tell me when you find out the answer.
我们不能把每个提到"黑傀"的信息都屏蔽
Seriously, we can't ban every use of the N-word.
对黑人的蔑称
你可以的  唯一的问题是怎么...
Yes, you can. The only question is how...
不  不  黛安  那样的话
Mm-mm. No, no, every rap lyric on the planet
这世界上所有的饶舌歌词就都没了
would go out the window, Diane.
那「哈克贝利·费恩历险记」呢
What about Huckleberry Finn?
因频繁使用"黑傀"一词而引起争议的小说  新版书将"黑傀"全数用"奴隶"替换
可以  那就很不幸了
Yes, that would be unfortunate.
所有引用「哈克贝利·费恩历险记」的推文也没了
All those times Huckleberry Finn is quoted in tweets.
问题在于  有研究表明
Here's the problem. They did a study that showed
推特上半数的性别歧视的真凶是女人
50% of Twitter's misogyny was perpetrated by women.
因此  如果我们屏蔽了
So, if we're banning
性别歧视和种族歧视的信息
misogynistic posts and racist posts...
等等  我也读过那篇论文  那是假的
Uh, wait, I read that study. It was bogus.
我也看过  它好像把"荡妇"和"淫妇"
Yeah, I did, too. It's like they just counted
都算作女性歧视了
the words "Slut" And "Whore" as misogynistic.
是的  而且许多女性
Right, and a lot of the women
是把"荡妇"用在"荡妇羞耻"的语境内
used the word "Slut" as in "Slut-shaming."
女性为自己的性行为或性欲感到羞耻或低人一等的行为
这也支持了我的论点
Which supports my contention.
我们需要在语言上持中立态度
We need to be language neutral.
是的  但你可不是这么说的
Yeah, but that's not what you said.
好的  我这就走
Yeah, I'm going.
那是谁啊
Who is that?
我好无聊
I'm bored.
教我点东西吧
Teach me something.
说正经的呢
Come on, seriously.
教教我怎么干你这行
Teach me how to do your job.
我也能当调查员
I could be an investigator.
那是什么  你为什么要那样弄照片
What's that? Why are you doing that to the photos?
测量子弹壳和尸体之间的距离
Measuring the distance between the shell casing and the body.
天啊  这张好恐怖
God, this one's grisly.
你亲眼见过尸体吗
Have you ever seen a dead body in person?
见过
Yes.
-多少具  -六具
- How many? - Six.
我见过12具
I've seen 12.
公交车上的自杀式炸弹
Suicide bomb on a bus.
我是刚刚事发就赶到现场的
I got to the scene just afterwards.
那样稀松平常真是奇怪
It's weird how normal it was.
-可能吧  -除了孩子
- Can be. - Except for the kid.
婴儿手推车里有个小宝宝
There was a baby in a stroller.
你想知道什么
Okay, what do you want to know?
-你是怎么当上调查员的  -考个证
- How do you become an investigator? - Get a license.
没有证就不能调查了吗
I can't investigate unless I have a license?
也可以  但是会被抓
Well, you can, but you'll get caught.
天啊  这个国家就是这样打击积极性的
God, that's what's killing initiative in this country.
干什么都得有个证
Everything needs a license.
但是你可以辅助有证的调查员
Well, you can always assist a licensed investigator.
比如你
Like you?
不  不  我说的不是这个意思
No, no, that's not what I'm saying.
-但是你说了  -没有
- But you said it. - No.
我是概括性地说...
I said, in the abstract...
麻烦找一下玛娅·林德尔
Um, Maia Rindell, please.
好  她在里面  稍等
Yeah, she's in there. Hang on.
他们是美国公民吗
Are they American citizens?
-什么事  -你爸给你打电话了吗
- What? - Has your dad called you?
怎么了
Why?
天啊  你看你
God, look at you.
你恨我
You hate me.
是你想要毁了我爸
You're trying to destroy my dad.
-我应该怎样表现  -我没有毁掉亨利
- How should I look? - I'm not destroying Henry.
我只是不想让他毁了我
I'm just trying to keep him from destroying me.
还有你  我不是敌人
And you. I'm not the enemy here.
你提交了证据
You turned evidence.
因为你爸也这么做了
Because your dad was doing the same.
好了
Okay, good.
我们谈过了  我们了解彼此了
We talked. We understand each other.
-你该走了  -玛娅
- You should go. - Maia,
接下来的一两天  你爸给你打电话
your dad is gonna call you in the next day or two
找你跟他面谈
and ask you to meet him to talk.
只有你们俩
Just the two of you.
他会弄得很家常  喝点东西什么的
He'll try to make it sound casual... drinks or something.
如果他这么做了  要拒绝他
If he does that, say no.
-为什么  -他会佩戴窃听器
- Why? - He'll be wearing a wire.
他会引导你说出一些证明我有罪的话
He'll try to get you to say something incriminating
还有公司的事
about me, about this firm.
甚至可能是关于你自己的
Maybe even about yourself.
我为什么要相信你
Why do I trust you?
因为我是你叔叔  我站在你的这边
Because I'm your uncle, and I'm on your side.
我叔叔  跟我妈婚外情的叔叔
My uncle, who is sleeping with my mom.
丽诺是这么说的吗
Is that what Lenore said?
我撞见你们两个了
I walked in on you two.
我得回去工作了
I've got to get back to work.
拒绝他  玛娅
Say no, Maia.
如果你爸打电话跟你谈
If your dad calls to talk to you,
跟他说你们不能见面
tell him you can't meet.
准备好了吗
Yeah, ready?
等下
Hold on. Whoa, whoa.
喂
Hello?
爸...  我...
Dad, uh... I've...
今晚不行了  抱歉
I can't do tonight, sorry.
怎么了
Oh. Why not?
工作
Work.
不然我去找你吧
Well, then, maybe I'll come to you.
不  不了  今晚不行
No, no, not tonight.
我看看过几天晚上行不行
Let me see if I can arrange another night.
玛娅  拜托了  我们要谈谈
Maia, please, we need to talk.
电话里讲吧
Tell me on the phone.
不好  还是当面说比较好
No, it's better if we do it in person.
明晚吧
Tomorrow night.
我看看能不能行
Let me see what I can do.
爱你
Love you.
埃尔斯贝特·塔肖尼
你知道我们的顾虑
You know what the worry is.
我们制定的规则会被用于政治目的
Our rules are gonna be used for political ends.
我们只是单纯地被要求创造出一种民主的氛围
We have simply been asked to create a civil atmosphere...
不是这样  他们要求我们制定合理的规则
No, we've been asked to create fair rules
来赶走这些人
for expelling members.
如果这些人都是保守派的...
If all of those members are conservative...
-他们不全是保守派的  -他们就是
- They aren't all conservative. - Yes, they are.
我们经手的每个案例都是关于
Every example we've used is about
激进的反堕胎人士在威胁
passionate pro-lifers intimidating
可怜的  无助的同意堕胎合法的人
poor, helpless little pro-choicers.
那是因为威胁来自于右翼
That's because the intimidation is coming from the right.
但是审查机制的人是站在左翼的
Well, the censorship is coming from the left!
科林·莫雷洛
去他的工作  现在过来见我
不  但我有个...  我能不能...
No, but I have a... could I...
大伙  大伙  能听我说两句吗
Guys? Guys. Could I please say something?
最关键的问题是得看语境  对吗
Okay, the problem here is and always will be contexted, right?
我们没法制定出一个一劳永逸的规则
I mean, we can't create one-size-fits-all rules,
所以我们只需要一个上诉机制
so what we need is an appeal process.
继续讲
Keep going.
比如说有一个人骚扰超过了13次
Well, say someone harasses more than 13 times,
或是威胁他人超过两次
or threatens more than twice.
那他们的作品就只能经过审查后
They are kept from posting any more until a panel
才能发布
reviews their work.
我们会给这个用户一个机会
Then the person is given the chance
为他  或者她申辩
to defend him or herself.
大家同意这个观点吗
Can we agree on that?
朱利叶斯
Julius?
-同意  -很好
- Yes. - Good.
那我们现在就只用考虑上诉机制了
So we just kicked our problem down the road to an appeal process.
这不是很好吗
Doesn't it feel good?
*Work for that money get that money for the work*
*Then I spit the hottest verse*
*When I'm flying around the Earth*
-你们这些另类右翼真可耻
-问题在你们身上  朋友  你们没有安全感  无法面对现实不能赖在另类右翼的人身上
*Cash in hand I'll turn a penny to a grand*
提交
*When I'm ready, I'm-a land rockin' steady for my fans*
*Never hesitant 'bout these dead presidents*
你暂时不能发布消息  需要上诉  请点击下方链接
*Tuck my Benjamins, yeah I'll be NNM...*
挺有意思
This is gonna be fun.
*Do another show...*
进来吧  请坐
So come on in. Um, have a seat.
抱歉  他们还没有把我的家具送来
Sorry, they still haven't delivered my furniture.
没关系
Oh, well, that's okay.
感觉这里还差点烧烤和帅哥
Feels like we should have barbecue and Franks here.
我爸打电话给我了...
My dad called. Um...
他想和我单独会面  没有律师在场
he wanted to meet, alone, without a lawyer.
好吧  这并不能说明什么
Okay, well, that's not necessarily anything.
我叔叔贾克斯  他警告我我爸会佩戴窃听器
My Uncle Jax, he warned me that my dad would wear a wire.
你能不能  把桌子上的
Could you, um, reach up there
笔记本拿给我
and hand me that pad there?
这是刚刚发生的事吗
Oh, so, this just happened?
是的  是的  今天的事
Uh, yeah, yeah, today.
我爸  他想今晚和我见面
My dad, he wanted to meet tonight,
-但我推掉了  -好姑娘
- but I said I couldn't. - Good girl.
播放好姑娘的「好人」
Playing "Goodie," By Good Girl.
不  停
No. Stop.
艾达  停
Ada, stop.
抱歉  这是范塔西娅给我的
Sorry, it's this thing Fantasia got me.
艾达  停止播放
Ada, stop playing!
加大音量
Volume up.
继续  它会自己停的
Go ahead, it wears itself out.
我该怎么做
What should I do?
我知道我希望你怎么做
I know what I want you to do,
-但也许你不想这么做  -什么
- but you may not want to. - What?
我说我知道我希望你怎么做
Uh, I said I know what I want you to do.
不不  这句我听见了...
No, no, no, I heard that. Um...
你希望我怎么做
What do you want me to do?
给他提供假消息
Feed him false information.
你认识特拉维斯·利奥波德吗
Do you know who Travis Leopold is?
-不认识  -他是一名房地产大亨
- No. - He's a real estate magnate
给了你们律所800万
with $8 million in business at your law firm.
-我从没听说过他  -因为是我刚编的
- I never heard of him. - Because I just made him up.
要是你爸问起你的工作  装作很忧虑的样子
If your dad asks about your business, act worried.
他会问你忧虑什么
He'll ask you why you're worried.
你就告诉他你不能说
You tell him you can't talk about it.
如果他没问了  他就没有戴窃听器
If he lets it go, he's not wearing a wire.
但如果他追问下去
But if he pushes you,
你就告诉他阿德里安·博斯曼为利奥波德先生
tell him Adrian Boseman backdated earnings
倒填了收益日期  帮他逃税
for Mr. Leopold to help him with his taxes.
利奥波德先生就给了你们律所
And Mr. Leopold gifted your firm
80万作为回报
with a bonus of $800,000.
我做不到
I can't do that.
是  是
Yeah, yeah.
我就说了你可能不愿意这么做
That's why I said you might not want to do it.
还有一个方法就是别去见你爸
I mean, the other option is don't see your dad.
好吧...
Okay, um...
-起来吧  -谢谢
- Oh. Here we go. - Thank you.
但如果你要这么做  记得录音
Oh, uh, but if you do do it, record it.
就把手机打开  然后...
Just turn on your iPhone and, uh...
点一下"录音"键
...hit "Record."
你明晚想跟我一起吃晚饭吗
Wanna have dinner with me tomorrow night?
晚饭...
Dinner...
还是正式晚饭
or dinner dinner?
你得说说有什么不同
You'll have to explain the difference.
晚饭就是上床
Dinner is fucking.
正式晚饭就是约会  然后再上床
Dinner dinner is a date, then fucking.
好吧  是正式晚饭
Mm, okay. Dinner dinner.
不去
No.
你好  我是菲利克斯·斯塔普斯
Hi, I'm Felix Staples.
我的偶像是克里斯托弗·希钦斯
My heroes are Christopher Hitchens,
克里斯托弗·希钦斯：美国最负盛名的专栏作家、记者、评论员
温德姆·刘易斯  安德鲁·布雷巴特
Wyndham Lewis, Andrew Brietbart,
温德姆·刘易斯：英国现代派运动"漩涡主义"的创立者
安德鲁·布雷巴特：美国激进右翼网络媒体创始人
伊扎克·拉宾和莉儿·金
Yitzhak Rabin, and Lil' Kim.
伊扎克·拉宾：以色列总理  1995年被刺杀
莉儿·金：美国饶舌黑人女歌手
你好  斯塔普斯先生
Hello, Mr. Staples.
我们是来听你的上诉的
We've been appointed to hear your appeal.
很好  介意我站着吗
Great. Mind if I stand?
我...  请便
I... Please do.
你上次大选投给谁了
Who did you vote for in the last election?
-什么  -总统大选你投给谁了
- Excuse me? - Who did you vote for for president?
-我不便回答你的问题  -为什么
- I'm not gonna answer that. - Why not?
这与上诉无关
It's irrelevant.
是吗  你们的政治倾向与这次上诉无关
Really? Your politics are irrelevant to this?
博斯曼先生  你为希拉里·克林顿捐了8564美元
Mr. Boseman, you gave $8,564 to Hillary Clinton.
戴安·洛克哈特  你给了...
Diane Lockhart, you gave...
你是从哪儿得来这些消息的
Where'd you get that?
公众记录  希拉里18860美元
Public records. $18,860 to Hillary.
芭芭拉·科斯达
Barbara Kolstad,
你给了...23万  等下  我查下...
you gave $23,000 to, wait, let me check...
不想搞错了
hmm, want to get this right.
希拉里
Hmm. Hillary.
那我呢
What about me?
你怎么了
What about you?
-我给捐了特朗普多少钱  -不知道
- How much money did I give to Trump? - I don't know.
我没有查你的捐款
I didn't check your contribution
因为这不能论证我要陈述的事实
'cause it doesn't fit my narrative.
7500美元
$7,500.
很好  你的故事是你的
Great. Write your own narrative.
我要说的是我是你们政治正确下的
Mine is that I'm a martyr
殉难者
to your political correctness.
-也许不是你的  -我赢了
- Maybe not yours. - I win.
我想你会在前五分钟
I guessed you would say "Political correctness"
提到"政治正确"
within the first five minutes.
真"有意思"
Well, that was almost funny.
你们现在处境不佳  没必要卖弄幽默
You know, you're in an unfortunate position to be funny
因为你们都是汤姆·布勒和凯蒂·布勒
because you're all Tom and Katie Buellers.
汤姆·布勒是谁
Who is Tom Bueller?
他们是费利·布勒的父母
They're the parents in Ferris Bueller.
「春天不是读书天」：美国喜剧电影
没人喜欢我父母
Nobody likes the parents.
大家都喜欢我
Everybody likes me.
对不  有趣的家伙  什么都不在乎的家伙
Right? The funny guy. The guy who doesn't care.
了解了  斯塔普斯先生
Good to know, Mr. Staples.
这就是你的申诉吗  你很有趣
Is that your appeal, that you're funny?
一部分是这样  但首先我想知道
In part, but first I'd like
你们为什么封禁我的账号
to know why you banned me.
我们先从你的反犹太人言论开始吧
Well, let's start with your anti-Semitic posting.
好啊  开始吧
Okay, let's do it.
"我读到你的留言"
"When I read your posts..."
有时候我觉得我们需要进行一次外科手术式屠杀
...sometimes I think we need a surgical holocaust.
把讨厌的犹太人都干掉
Just kill the irritating Jews.
怎么了
Yes?
这是你的申诉  不是我们的
It's your appeal, not ours.
我本人就是犹太人  行过割礼了
Well, I'm Jewish, circumcised.
我可以现在就掏出来给你们看
I can show you right now.
我当时是在和另一位批评内塔尼亚胡
Uh, I was arguing with another Jew who criticized Netanyahu
内塔尼亚胡：以色列总理
并想把笑脸贴纸贴到
and wanted to paste happy face stickers
所有巴基斯坦人脸上的犹太人争论
on all the Palestinian faces.
所以我脱口而出了这句会伤害到他的话
So I said what I knew would hurt him.
你是想说
Are you arguing that
犹太人就不可能反犹了吗
someone who's Jewish can't be anti-Semitic?
不
No.
我想说的是我的评论是政治言论
I'm arguing my post was political
而不是反犹太人言论
and not anti-Semitic.
对吗  我本可以这么写
Right? I-I could've written
"恕我直言  先生  我不同意你的观点"
"With all due respect, sir, I disagree with you."
当然可以这么说  但那就伤不到他了
Sure, but that wouldn't have hurt him.
-而我想伤到他  -造成身体上的伤害吗
- And I wanted to hurt him. - Physically?
不  我想让他哭
No, I wanted to make him to cry.
我想让他因为他那些被反犹分子屠杀的
I want to make him cry for his poor dead ancestors slaughtered
已故先人而哭
by anti-Semites.
我明白你想在这里把自己粉饰成受害者
I understand you want to make yourself the victim here,
斯塔普斯先生  但实际上你是
Mr. Staples, but you are
一位另类右翼势力领导者
a leader of the alt-right.
另类右翼都讨厌同性恋  不是吗
The alt-right, ma'am, hates gays, don't they?
-大多数是这样  -他们讨厌同性恋婚姻
- Well, for the most part. - They hate gay marriage,
他们信教  他们是保守主义者
they're religious, they're conservative,
而我
and yet, I... do...
戴米恩
Damian?
我并不想这样的
I didn't want to have to...
戴米恩是我花50美元叫来的同性恋男妓
Damian is a gay prostitute
-他可以当场给我口交  -好了  够了
- whom I paid $50 to blow me right now. - Okay. All right.
这买卖太划算了实在不能错过
Too good of a deal to pass up.
跟你们说了我是犹太人
Told you I was Jewish.
好了  好了  我们明白你的意思了
All right, all right, you made your point.
现在这里谁是保守主义者
Who's the conservative?
谁又是恐同者  先生
Who's the homophobe, sir?
反正不是我
Not me.
如果可能的话  我立刻就可以
Look, I would... I'd be a heterosexual in a second,
变成一位异性恋
if I could be,
但我愿意当着你们的面
but I'm willing to be fellated
被人吹箫
in front of this panel
因为我相信美国  戴米恩  开吹
because I believe in America. Damien!
好了
Okay.
-*我的双眼已经看到了*  -好了  够了
- *Mine eyes have seen the glory* - All right. Okay.
-*主将要降临的荣耀*  -好了
- *Of the coming of the Lord* - Yeah.
*他踏过*
*He has trampled ev...*
上帝啊  真是个极品
God, talk about a piece of work.
他在博宣传  他这是在试图挑衅我们
He's looking for publicity, he's trying to provoke us.
所以  我们不上他的套
So, we don't engage.
我们就仅仅咬住他写的信息
We stick to his posts.
如果我们以政治作为论点  我们就输了
See, if we debate politics, we lose.
扎克·迪瓦恩
晚上喝两杯听起来不错  把地方告诉我
他想把脏水引到我们身上  你看
He's trying to make it about us, you see.
你想要怎样
What do you need?
我知道明天还有一次申诉听证会
Uh, I know we have another session tomorrow,
我只是  我向先提前道个歉
but I just... I want to apologize ahead of time.
道歉什么
For?
网上的人
People on the interwebs
或许会说些你们的坏话
might have nasty things to say about you guys,
我只是想让你知道  我与此无关
I just want you to know, I have nothing to do with it.
知道了
Good to know.
你让我想起了我妈妈
You remind me of my mom.
她是位老师
She was a school teacher.
她教我要去爱我的同胞
And she taught me to love my fellow man,
如果我们都去拥抱我们的敌人
and if we all just hug our enemies,
就会迎来千年的和平
peace would last 1,000 years.
所以你现在这样是叛逆吗
So this is rebellion?
不  只是博人一笑
No, this is having a laugh.
你笑得太少了  洛哈特女士
You don't smile enough, Mrs. Lockhart.
你应该在生活中多找点乐子
You need to get more joy out of life.
拜拜  老妈
Bye, Mom.
-梅丽莎  -在
- Marissa? - Yeah.
在查查网上找找
Check the Chummy sites
有没有关于我们或者律所的新留言
for any new comments on our firm, or on us.
行  我们要找什么样的留言
Sure. What are we looking for?
-威胁  骚扰言论  -没问题
- Threats. Harassment. - No problem.
戴安
Oh, Diane?
你指的是不是
You mean like,
"如果你强奸一位女律师"
"Is it considered rape..."
这算不算强奸呢
...if you rape a female lawyer?
告诉我  洛哈特女士
Tell me, Ms. Lockhart,
如果我强奸了一位女律师  你能帮我脱罪吗
could you get me off if I raped a female lawyer?
这还有一条
And here's another.
还有两条
Ugh, and two more.
你想让我把这些留言转发给你吗
Do you want me to forward these to you?
是的  麻烦了
Uh, yes, please.
查查交友网  戴安·洛哈特的个人主页
是的  我希望你被强奸  但从法律的角度上说
Yes, I hope you get raped, but for legal purposes,
我不打算亲自强奸你
I do not intend to rape you myself.
查查交友网  戴安·洛哈特的个人主页
留言因涉及不当言论而被移除
他们知道把不当言论控制在13条以下
They know to keep it under 13 posts.
-什么  -那些另类右翼
- What? - The alt-righters.
他们一直在给我们发骚扰留言
They've been sending us harassing posts.
而每个人都只发了12条
And each person has only sent 12.
他们是怎么知道要这么做的
And how do they know to do that?
我不知道
I don't know.
封禁规则是我们私下讨论得出的
The rules were discussed in private session.
有人泄密了吗
Did someone leak?
-杰  -我尽力去查查看
- Jay? - I'll do what I can, uh,
但这些另类右翼分子
but these alt-right guys,
我猜他们是不会愿意和我交谈的
my guess is they're not gonna want to talk to me.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
收到你的短信我很惊讶
I was surprised to get your text.
我们好久没联系了
It's been forever.
是啊
Yeah.
这里有鹰嘴豆吗  还是只有薯条
Do they have hummus here, or is it just chips?
什么
What?
他们这里有正餐吗  还是只有酒水
Uh, do they have real food here, or is it just drinks?
我正在控制饮食排毒
I'm on this detox.
如果你吃了八根薯条
I mean, if you eat eight chips,
那就是摄入了142卡路里
that's 142 calories.
我不知道
Uh, I-I don't know.
-而且所有人都在讨论鳄梨是多么健康  -什么
- And everyone goes on about how healthy guacamole is. - What?
你今天过得如何
How are you doing?
很好  你呢
Good, how are you?
很好
Good.
嗨  哥们
Hey, man.
这位是扎克
Oh, this is Zack.
你好  扎克  很高兴认识你  我叫科林
Hey, Zack, nice to meet you. Colin.
是的  我也是  好强的握力啊
Yeah, you too. Good grip. Pfft.
你平时在哪锻炼
Where do you work out?
我啊  没去健身房
Uh... I... nowhere.
我就  我就在家玩玩哑铃
I just, uh... it's just some weights at home.
如果你想要认真健身的话  这是我的名片
If you want to get serious, here's my card.
-认真健身  -是的
- Serious? - Yeah.
谢谢  你们俩怎么认识的
Uh, thanks. How do you two know each other?
我是卢卡的私教
Oh, I'm Lucca's personal trainer.
-真的吗  -是的
- Really? - Mm-hmm.
那你指导得不错啊
Well, you're doing a great job. -
总之  我该  我该走了
Anyway, I should, uh, I should head out.
你们俩晚上好好玩
Uh, hey, have a good evening.
是的  你也是
Yeah, you too.
他挺不错的
He's a nice guy.
和他之间有什么故事吗
What's his story?
你晚上看起来很心不在焉
You seem distracted tonight.
录音中
玛娅
Maia!
看看谁来了
Look who's here.
玛娅  亲爱的
Maia, darling.
什么情况
What's going on?
你爸之前心情有点低落
Oh, your dad was feeling blue,
于是临时给他弄了一场派对
so last minute, I threw him a party.
是你爸打电话叫你过来的吗
Did Dad call you?
是的  昨天叫的
Yeah, yesterday.
亨利  瞧瞧谁来了  是玛娅
Henry, look who's here, Maia.
天啊  我好想你
Oh, my God, I missed you.
快进来
Ah, come on in.
我在帮厨子做披萨
I'm helping the caterers make pizzas.
谢谢
Aw, thank you.
他可想死你了
He's been missing you.
快来  快过来
Come, come, come.
看看你们
Look at you two here.
我正在跟她说  我有多怀念
I was just saying how much I missed us,
一家团聚的感觉
being together.
应该找机会再一起去波拉波拉岛
Bora Bora, we need to go back.
保罗一家已经准备要走了
The Pauls are-are getting ready to leave.
-我帮他们叫辆车  -好的
- Oh, I'll get an Uber. - Yeah.
他们都喝得太醉了
They're too drunk.
你还好吗  玛娅
How are you, Maia?
很好
Good.
你看起来很高兴  爸爸
You seem happy, Dad.
是的  没错
Yeah, yeah,
我想是的  我是说  这是几周来
I guess I am. I mean, this is the first time
我第一次感觉到正常
I've felt normal in weeks.
是啊  没错  我也是
Mm-hmm, yeah, oh, me too.
就好像回到了八岁的时候
Feels like when I was eight.
工作上还顺利吗
And work is going well?
还不错
It is. Mm.
你吃饭的时候看起来心事重重的
You seemed a little worried at dinner.
没出什么事吧
Nothing wrong?
没什么  没事
Nothing, no.
毕竟  工作就是  这样
I mean, work is... work.
没错
Yeah.
或者  你有没有任何事想跟我聊聊
I mean, anything you want to talk about?
没有
No.
没关系的  我是你爸爸
I mean, come on, it's your dad.
你什么事都可以告诉我
You can tell me anything.
就是
It's just...
我永远搞不清楚界限在哪里  你明白吗
I can never quite tell where that line is, you know?
合法或不合法的界限
Between the legal and the illegal.
什么事情呢
What issue?
他问了你工作上的事情
He asked you about work?
是  但也许只是  正常的闲聊
Yeah, but it might've just been, you know, talking.
可能只是  我不知道  作为父亲关心而已
Just... I don't know, being a dad. I...
我讨厌这样
I hate this.
我知道  我很抱歉
I know. I'm sorry.
你告诉他特拉维斯·利奥波德的事了吗
Did you tell him about Travis Leopold?
是的
Yeah.
没错
家庭生活不易
Family's hard.
是啊  没错
Yeah, yeah.
艾达  放点温暖好听的
Uh, Ada, play something nice.
温暖好听的
Playing something nice.
*他用指尖撩拨我的苦楚*
*Strumming my pain with his fingers*
*他用词曲唱出我的一生*
*Singing my life with his words*
*他用歌声温柔地杀死我*
*Killing me softly with his song*
*温柔地杀死我*
*Killing me softly...*
你好  你知道艾伦在哪吗
Hi, do you know where Aaron is?
菲利克斯让我给他传个口信
I'm supposed to get him some kind of message from Felix.
你是谁
Who are you?
梅丽莎  怎么  你认识艾伦吗
Marissa. Why, do you know Aaron?
也许吧  怎么了
I might. Why?
我有点赶时间
Look, I don't have a lot of time.
如果你看到他  告诉他梅丽莎来过
If you see him, tell him Marissa dropped by,
还有我非常喜欢他那条"七不等于八"的信息
and I love his "Seven doesn't equal eight" post.
不好意思
Uh, s-sorry,
我最近得到太多莫名其妙的关注了
I just get a lot of unwanted attention.
我是艾伦
I'm Aaron.
真的吗  你写的东西都太棒了
Seriously? Your stuff is so great.
谢谢  大部分都是晚上琢磨出来的
Thanks, it's mostly my late night stuff.
你有什么需要吗
What do you need?
菲利克斯让我来联系你
Felix told me to get in touch with you.
他想先暂时不管四叶论坛
He wants to stay off 4chan for a while.
他说我们应该发不超过15条的恐吓信息
He said we shouldn't exceed, like, 15 threatening posts.
不对  是13条  不能超过13
No, 13, stay below 13.
有人说上限更大了  他们认识查查网的人
Someone said it was more. They know someone in Chumhum.
不对  这应该由审查小组制定
No, this is from the censorship panel.
菲利克斯有他们的记录副本
Felix has their transcripts.
原来如此
Good to know.
回头见
See you around.
等等  什么意思
Wait a minute, what?
他有你们的商议记录副本
He has your transcripts from your deliberations.
怎么拿到的
How?
不知道
We don't know.
可能是有人泄露的
Looks like someone leaked.
你觉得是谁
Who do you think?
-不管是谁我都会很惊讶  -是啊
- That would surprise me. - Yeah.
你叫什么名字来着
Um, what is your name again?
-梅丽莎  -梅丽莎
- Marissa. - Marissa.
能不能请你先出去一下呢  梅丽莎
Would you step outside for a second, Marissa, please?
谢谢
Thank you.
杰
Jay...
查查朱利叶斯  看看是不是他泄露的
Check out Julius. See if he leaked.
好的
Sure.
我们今天要聊点什么呢
What shall we talk about today?
你发的信息  先生
Your posts, sir.
这里的事情都是因为你的信息
This is all about your posts.
-戴安  -真是太完美了
- Diane. - How fitting.
洛哈特小姐和我关系很好的  不是吗
Uh, Ms. Lockhart and I have a certain rapport, don't we?
斯塔普斯先生  请解释一下有关
Mr. Staples, please explain your posts
堕胎合法化激进分子  迪莱拉·米斯的信息
regarding the pro-choice activist Dahlila Mills.
迪莱拉·米斯  迪莱拉·米斯
Dahlila Mills. Dahlila Mills.
迪莱拉·米斯
Dahlila Mills...
是个好名字  可我就是想不起来了
Beautiful name. I... can't place it.
是的  我暴怒的时期
Ah! Yes. My days of rage.
我们来尽点自己的本分吧
Let's all do our part.
消灭迪莱拉·米斯的基金  有人想捐款吗
Who wants to contribute to a fund to take out Dahlila Mills?
告诉我  斯塔普斯先生
Tell me, Mr. Staples,
这为什么不是一个可以起诉的恐吓呢
why is that not an actionable threat?
因为我没有在恐吓她啊
Because I'm not threatening her.
我说"消灭她"  并不是"杀了她"的意思
I don't mean "Take her out" as in "Kill her."
我的老天爷  你把我当什么禽兽了
My goodness, what kind of monster do you think I am?
我只是说
I'm talking about
不要让她在出现在辩论中
taking her out of the debate.
那你如何让某人不再出现在辩论中呢
And how do you take someone out of a debate?
不知道啊  痛骂她  让她难堪
I don't know. Shout her down, embarrass her.
你为什么会需要这样的基金呢
Why do you need funds for that?
那你又为什么需要基金来买裙子呢
Why do you need funds for that dress?
因为我不想沦落到穿你那衣服的地步
Because I don't want to end up in that jacket.
咱们法庭上可有的吵了
Oh! I will see you in court.
再问一次  你为什么需要基金来阻止某人
Again, why do you need funds to shut someone down?
我想不到有趣的答案  所以我拒绝回答
I can't think of anything funny, so I decline to reply.
当你写完那个之后
Well, after you wrote that,
米斯女士收到了这些信息
these posts were sent to Ms. Mills.
-"我们会来抓到你的"  -记得锁好门
- "We're coming to get you, be..." - ...sure to lock your doors,
因为宪法第二修正案就是为你这种人设立的
'cause the Second Amendment was made for people like you.
宪法第二修正案：人民持有及携带武器的权利
你知道近距离用格洛克手枪打哈密瓜会什么样吗
You ever see what a Glock does to cantaloupe close up?
事后打扫你的浴室太麻烦了
It's hard to clean up in your shower.
最简单的方法就是恶意人肉搜索
The easiest thing is to just dox you.
恶意人肉搜索：在网上恶意公布某人的私人信息
明天用下信用卡吧
Try using your credit card tomorrow.
看看会发生什么
See what happens.
贱人  贱人  烂货  贱人
Bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, double-cunt, bitch...
"贱人  贱人"
"...bitch, bitch."
听起来火气可真不小
Wow, they all sound angry.
这些人和正在网上攻击我们的是同一批人
These are the same accounts now harassing us,
因为是你让他们这么做的
because you told them to.
瞧你说的  好像我对这些人有秘密的操控能力
You act like I have some secret control over people.
不  不是什么秘密
No, not secret.
你有证据支持你的观点吗
Do you have some proof to back up this contention?
当然
Yes.
一位叫艾伦·福勒的人声称  你直接告诉他
An Aaron Fowler claimed you directly told him
让他将骚扰我们的信息数量控制在13以下
to keep his harassment of this panel to under 13 posts.
其实  唯一比汤姆和凯蒂·布勒更悲哀的是
Do you know, the only thing sadder than Tom and Katie Bueller
费力·布勒在满口谎话时被揭穿
is a sputtering Ferris Bueller caught in a lie.
老天  你简直和我妈一模一样
God, you are exactly like my mom.
-我能给你读几条信息吗  -请
- Can I read you a few posts? - Please.
我们希望尽最大可能给你机会来为自己辩护
We want to give you every opportunity to defend yourself.
这是一位堕胎合法化激进分子发给我的
This is to me from a pro-choice activist.
去死吧  我希望你在给南方乡巴佬
"Go to..." ...hell. I hope you choke on the cocks
吹箫的时候噎死
of the southern rednecks you're blowing.
这明显还是一个种族歧视的激进分子
Now this is clearly a racist pro-choice activist,
因为我们都知道那里应该是黑色的
because it's well known the cocks in question are black.
不信的话  你可以查一下我的交友信息
You can check my dating profile.
后面还有呢
There's more.
-"他们首先会来"  -反对我堕胎的权利
- "First they'll come..." - ...for my abortion rights,
接着就是你们的基佬婚姻  你这自怨自艾的犹太佬
then they'll come for your gay marriage, you self-hating kike.
"犹太佬」  后面还有其他的
"Kike." And there are more.
如你所见  我很好奇为什么我会成为目标
So you can see, I'm wondering why I'm being targeted
因为反正堕胎合法化阵营也是一样丑恶
when the pro-choice side is just as ugly.
如果能跟你们一样程度  我们会关注的
If its ugliness matches yours, it will be addressed.
我们并没有针对某一方的意思
We're not targeting any one side.
但是  从你们的商议记录来看
And yet, in your transcripts from your deliberations...
先等等  等一
Wait a second, wait a...
-你有我们的记录副本  -我想是的
- You have our transcripts? - I believe I do.
你知道那是版权信息吗
And you know that's proprietary information?
这上面没有相关声明
It doesn't say so.
查查网可以就此事起诉你
Chumhum could sue you for that.
不  他们可以起诉泄露信息的人
No, they could sue the person who leaked it.
我只是个想向社会
I'm just the citizen-journalist
传达信息的公民记者
wanting to communicate it to the world.
无论如何  在之前的讨论中
Anyway, in this earlier discussion,
科斯达女士  你用非常不雅的言词
Ms. Kolstad, you shouted down Julius Cain
大声喝止朱利叶斯·凯恩的发言
in language most indecorous.
我认为你将"汤姆叔叔"用作了动词[卑躬屈膝]
I believe you used the word "Uncle Tom" as a verb.
他真是个混蛋
He's a fucking asshole.
他试图让别人觉得我们很虚伪
And he's trying to make us look hypocritical.
他是个卑鄙的混账种族主义者
He's a racist little motherfucker.
那我们要怎么做
So what do we do?
等一下  这是怎么回事
Wait a minute. What is it?
我的天呐
Oh, my God.
我们律所什么时候变成马戏团了
When did this law firm become a circus?
戴安  你现在有空吗
Diane. Do you have a second?
斯塔普斯先生  如果你想说什么
If you have something to say, Mr. Staples,
就在委员会全体成员面前说  不要只对我说
say it in front of the whole committee, not just me.
-但我不喜欢他们  -因为你是种族主义者
- But I don't like them. - Because you're racist.
不是
No.
是  我对整个黑人群体都没有好感
And yes, I don't like blacks as a group.
不过这偏题了
But that's beside the point.
你想没想过尼尔·格罗斯为什么会选这家律所
Have you ever wondered why Neil Gross chose this firm
来主管他的服务条款审查委员会
to be in charge of his TOS committee?
你显然是想向我透露什么  那就说吧
You obviously want to tell me something, so tell me.
让一个黑人组成的律所
Putting an all-black law firm
负责他的审查委员会
in charge of his censorship committee?
你觉得这说得通吗
Does that make sense to you?
再见  斯塔普特先生
Good-bye, Mr. Staples.
再见  戴安·洛哈特
Good-bye, Diane Lockhart.
我承诺过要向你们做案件进度报告的
I promised to give you a progress report on your case.
所以我来啦
So, hi, here I am.
我向亨利·林德尔泄露了一个假消息
Anyway, I leaked a fictitious story to Henry Rindell
说贵所从一个虚构的客户那里接受了
about your firm receiving an $800,000 bribe
80万贿赂
from a fictitious client
来倒填其收入的日期
to backdate his earnings.
-什么  -是的  我知道
- Uh, w-what? - Yeah, I know.
不过我们可以利用这事来整克里斯特瓦
But we can use this to embarrass Kresteva.
塔肖尼女士  抱歉  我想得可能太简单了
Ms. Tascioni, I'm sorry to be prosaic in my thinking,
但这也不太像复杂情况
but this doesn't seem like a baroque matter.
我们没有做错任何事
We didn't do anything wrong.
你为什么要误导调查员呢
Why are you misleading the investigator?
好问题
Good question.
如果这个调查员是诚实的
And if this investigator were honest,
我会觉得你是对的
I would say you were right.
不过  虽然我不想如此评价任何人
But... and I hate to say this about any person...
迈克·克里斯特瓦习惯说谎
Mike Kresteva tends to lie.
那你需要我们做什么呢
So what do you need from us?
如果你们从别人那里听说了这80万美元贿金
If you hear about this $800,000 gift from anyone,
就意味着亨利·林德尔在跟我们作对
that means Henry Rindell is working against us,
而且我们也许能利用这一点
and we might be able to use it.
新装修公寓开放参观日
我要做什么
So what do I do?
表现得年轻甜蜜一点
Act young and sweet.
我们要扮演什么人
Who are we?
任何人都可以
Anyone we want.
天呐  我喜欢这个工作
God, I love this job.
我需要一副眼镜  我想扮一个地质学家
I need glasses. I want to be a geologist.
不行  这不是动画片
No, this isn't a cartoon.
好吧  你是个产品分析师
All right? You're a product analyst.
没人会问产品分析师是什么
No one asks what that is.
需要为你们介绍一下吗
Do you want a setup?
-当然  -你好  我们想在卢普区
- Sure. - Hi, we're just in the market
找个两居室
for a two bedroom in the Loop,
我们看到这里就停下进来看看  对吧  杰
so we saw this and we skidded to a stop, didn't we, Jay?
他不喜欢我这样喋喋不休地说话
Oh, God, he hates when I rattle on like that.
但是我们很爱对方  我还有什么好说的呢
But we love each other, so what can I say?
年轻人的爱情  有感染力
Young love. It's infectious.
对吧  像瘟疫一样
Isn't it? Like the plague.
这里作为年轻情侣的第一间公寓是很不错的
Well, this is a very good starter apartment for young couples.
尤其是年轻的职场人士
Especially young professionals.
他们从郊区蜂拥而来
They're all flocking back from the suburbs
因为他们想要住的离餐厅近一些
because they want to be near the restaurants
-还有酒吧  -像我们一样  杰  跳舞
- and the clubs. - Sounds like us, Jay. Dancing.
没错
That's right.
你们在卢普区工作吗
Do you work in the Loop?
是的
Yes.
我是个产品分析师
Well, I work as a product analyst,
但我想当个地质学家
but I want to be a geologist.
杰不希望我做地质学家
Jay doesn't want me to.
你看起来很眼熟  我们认识吗
Hey, you look familiar, do I know you?
不  我觉得我们不认识
No, I don't think so.
我以前在哪里见过你呢
Yeah. Where have I seen you before?
在你给我看的那个东西里
On that thing that you showed me. Um...
对了  那上面有他的名字  叫什么
Oh, right. That thing involving what's his name,
菲利克斯
um, Felix...
斯塔普斯  没错
Staples! Right.
他是我男朋友
All right. He's my boyfriend.
但我们的政治观点很不同
But our politics are very different.
我给你们展示下厨房
Let me show you the kitchen.
没关系  我们的政治观点也不同
That's all right. Our politics are very different too.
他是个另类右翼吗
Wow, so he's the alt-right guy?
我不想在这里讨论这事
Shh. I'd rather not share that here.
他私底下是个很不一样的人
He's very different in private.
我理解
I understand.
他现在在做什么呢
But what's he doing now?
我听说他在尽力避免被下线
I heard he's trying to keep from being kicked offline.
是的  这些愚蠢的东西  他们要审查他
Yeah, this stupid thing. They're trying to censor him.
天呐  太讨厌了  他在与他们抗争吗
Oh, God, I hate that. Is he fighting them anyway?
-是的  -很好
- Yeah. - Good.
跟我说说他是如何抗争的吧  我很好奇
Tell me how. I'm curious.
网络地址追踪  搜索  99.0.2
你们怎么得到这个网络地址的
How did you get this I.P. Address?
从斯塔普斯的男朋友那里得到的
Uh, Staples's boyfriend.
他吹嘘菲利克斯掌握内部信息
He was bragging about how Felix had insider information.
而且他想卖给我们一间公寓
And he wanted to sell us a condo.
他给我们看了记录副本
He showed us the transcripts.
我们看到了元数据  包括网络地址
And we got to see the meta-data, including the I.P. Address.
我们的网络地址
Our I.P. Address?
不是
No.
那是谁的
Well, whose, then?
是朱利叶斯家吗
Is it Julius's home?
查查网有限责任公司
查查网的办公室
The offices of Chumhum.
好的
Okay.
我们停止调查吧
Okay, let's shut this down.
为什么
Why?
芭芭拉  我们的客户
Barbara, we have a client
也许不想让我们深入调查这件事
who may not want us digging into this stuff.
什么意思  是查查网泄露的信息  为什么
Well, what are you saying, Chumhum leaked this? Why?
因为我们被陷害了
Because we're being set up.
被谁陷害
By whom?
查查看菲利克斯·斯塔普斯
All right. Check and see if Felix Staples
是不是与查查网内部的什么人有关联
has any relationship at all to anybody inside of Chumhum.
-可能是任何人  -我不喜欢这样
- It could be anybody. - I'm not liking this.
我不喜欢这样
I don't like this.
奴隶制153年前就结束了
Slavery ended 153 years ago.
混蛋尼尔·格罗斯该清醒了
It's time for the fucking Neil Grosses to get over it.
美国正在被这些与尼尔·格罗斯一样愚蠢的人
America is being turned into a welfare state
转变成一个福利国家
by all these stupid Neil Grosses.
搜索愚蠢的尼尔·格罗斯
Dumb Neil Gross.
愚蠢的尼尔·格罗斯
查米朋友 愚蠢的尼尔·格罗斯
近期发布信息中包含愚蠢的尼尔·格罗斯的共4,386个结果
看到弗格森市所有的尼尔·格罗斯
Love seeing all the Neil Grosses in Ferguson,
打破窗户偷耐克  真好
breaking windows to steal Nikes.
和任何人的任何关系
Any relationship at all, to anybody...
我能占用你一点时间吗
Can I talk to you for a second?
有个另类右翼男孩非常喜欢我
One of the alt-right boys really likes me,
他认为我是他们中的一员
he thinks I'm one of them.
-你是怎么知道的  -没什么
- How do you even know... - It's nothing.
女人关注他们的时候他们就很容易被迷惑
They're easily confused when women offer them attention.
他给我发送了一个链接
Anyway, he sent me a link.
他们正想办法避开针对种族主义者
They're working to get around
使用"黑傀"的禁令
your racist N-word ban.
怎么做到呢
How?
当他们想说"黑傀"时
Whenever they mean N-word
就用尼尔·格罗斯代替
they instead type Neil Gross.
我可以把它们印出来  但有很多
Yeah. I can print up the posts, but there are a lot.
都是把尼尔·格罗斯作为关键词的种族主义段子
All racist jokes with Neil Gross as the punchline.
这事会很不好看的
That's not gonna go over well.
我讨厌游戏  所以少来这一套
I hate games, so knock it the fuck off.
我完全不知道你在说什么
I have no idea what you're talking about.
昨天你看到和我在一起的男人
That guy you saw me with last night...
-魔力迈克  -是的
- Oh, Magic Mike? - Yes.
你知道我跟他上过床
You know I fucked him.
我想到会是这样
I figured as much.
但你不在意
But you don't care.
你说得挺清楚的了
Well, uh, you made it pretty clear
我们之间的关系
that our relationship was, well,
并不是情侣关系
not really a relationship.
的确不是
It's not.
好吧
Okay.
我说说我对现况的看法
Let me take a shot at what I think is happening right now.
你担心我们之间的进展太过认真
You're worried that we're getting too serious,
所以就拒绝与我约会  转而邀请你的小白脸
so you turn down a date with me, and then you invite your boy toy
去一个我可能会见到他的地方
to a place where I might see him,
以此终结我们的"关系"
thus ending our "Relationship."
对吗
Am I right?
问题是  你现在来跟我争论
Problem is, now you're here, arguing with me,
反而证明了你的计划不起作用
which kind of proves your plan didn't work out,
我们的关系还没有终结
and our relationship isn't over.
我该怎么做
How'd I do?
我们走吧
Let's go.
去哪里
Where?
你决定
You decide.
*It's been a long time, hasn't it?*
*We walked a fine line*
*Under it*
*For so long*
*I'd like to understand*
*But I'm already gone*
*Everyone got old, didn't they?*
*Calloused and so cold*
*All the way down*
*Every day*
*I'd like to talk to you*
*But I'm turning my face away*
这是什么地方
What is this?
我家
My place.
所以你是有钱人
So, you're rich?
算是吧
I guess so.
会对你造成困扰吗
Does that bother you?
我不知道
I don't know.
能一会儿决定一下这会不会困扰你吗
Can we decide whether it bothers you later?
你们这群混蛋
You bastards.
你们认为是我泄密的
You thought I leaked?
你们搜查了我办公室
You searched my office.
不  我们不知道是不是你泄密的
No, we didn't know whether you leaked or...
是因为特朗普吧  与政治有关吧
This is about Trump. This is about politics.
朱利叶斯  这是为了保持律所的正直性
Julius, this is about maintaining the integrity of this firm.
不  我对你那么忠诚
No. I was loyal to you.
我曾是你最忠诚的员工
I was the most loyal employee you had.
我们得知道是谁泄密的
We had to know who was leaking.
那你们调查过戴安了吗
And did you investigate Diane?
调查过卢卡吗
Or Lucca?
调查过其他人吗
Or anybody else?
你们失去了最忠诚的员工
You just lost your most loyal employee.
哈特&斯蒂芬斯律师事务所
安德鲁·哈特
高级合伙人
你好  我是朱利叶斯·凯恩
Hi, this is Julius Cain.
你是对的
You were right.
我们得谈谈
I think we should talk.
他们用了我的名字
They're using my name?
是
Yes.
我不明白  怎么回事
I-I don't understand. How?
用来替代"黑傀"
As a replacement for the N-word.
什么  真的假的
What, seriously?
-真的  -为什么
- Yes. - Why?
他们知道你不会审查这个词
They know you can't censor it.
我的天
Oh, my God.
他们跟野蛮人一样
They're like savages.
我们该怎么做
So, what do we do?
最好是什么都别做
I'm not sure there's anything you can do.
他们就像是想惹怒父母的小孩
They're like kids wanting to upset Mommy and Daddy.
戴安  问题是
Well, here's the problem, Diane.
我确实很生气
I am upset.
我知道
I know.
他们这是针对那该死的委员会
You know, they're reacting to that damn committee.
嗯  他们试图绕过我们实施的新规则
Yeah. They're working around the new rules we implemented.
斯塔普斯搞出的这些麻烦必须要了结
This whole mess with Staples needs to end.
他有很多支持者
He's got too many followers,
他们威胁要离开我的网站
and they're threatening to leave my services,
了结此事
so make it end.
我们重新考虑过了
We've reconsidered.
"重新考虑"
"Reconsidered"?
我们准备解禁你的账号
We're prepared to overturn the ban
恢复你的使用权
and reinstate you.
什么
What?
别走啊  事情才开始变得有趣
No, things were just getting interesting.
-结束了  -我没...
- We're done. - I'm not...
谢谢
Thank you.
不  还没完呢  戴安
No, we're not done. Diane.
戴安  我还有很多...
Diane, I've got a number of po...
我...
I've...
戴安
Diane!
简直胡来
This is totally fucked!
我是来自我辩解的  然后你们就这么溜了
I am here defending myself and what? You all slink off?
斯塔普斯先生  都结束了
Mr. Staples. It's over. We're done.
我们接受了你的思路  回家吧
We took the oxygen from your room. Go home.
你看这则对我的新的人生攻击
I want you to read this new attack on me.
"去死吧  你个基佬  言论自由早就过时了
"Die, you cocksucker. Free speech is outmoded.
法律是由奴隶主书写的"
It's a law written by slave owners."
你还想怎么样  斯塔普斯先生
What do you want, Mr. Staples?
我们已经恢复了你的使用权
You've been reinstated.
我不接受
I don't accept your reinstatement.
你就是个小丑
You're a clown.
更糟的是你是个聪明的小丑
What's worse is you're a smart clown
偶尔说得还挺有道理
who occasionally has a point,
却因为与种族主义和厌女症混为一谈而毁了
a point you destroy by mixing it up with racism and misogyny
而这些你可能根本不认可
you probably don't even believe.
你小时候  有人拒绝了你  或是取笑你
When you were little, someone rejected you or made fun of you,
现在你也成为了这种刻薄的人
and now you get to be one of the mean guys,
取笑他人
making fun of others.
而你就是道德标杆  对此义愤填膺吗
And you get to be the principal? Outraged?
不  我只是有更重要的事要做
No, I just have better things to do.
是吗
Oh, really?
你以为这是对进步人士
You think this is some grand rebellion
和社交正义战士的光荣反抗  其实不是
against progressives and social justice warriors, it's not.
你只不过是个在角落尿裤子的小屁孩
You're just some kid in the corner pissing yourself,
知足吧
so have at it.
你输了  戴安
You've lost, Diane.
你很生气
And you're upset
因为我是言论自由的化身
'cause I'm the embodiment of free speech.
不
No,
不过我们不得不忍受你的无理取闹
but you are what we have to tolerate,
谢谢了
so thank you.
走吧
Now go.
Go.
所以并没有真正被禁的吗
So, there were no real expulsions?
有一个  但在申诉中被撤销了
One, but it was reversed on appeal.
就是斯塔普斯吗
That was Staples?
那你们审议会的泄露者呢
And, uh, the leak of your deliberations?
是你们泄露的
That was from you.
你是说我们泄露了审议会内容吗
You're saying we leaked your deliberations?
是
Yes.
-为什么  -我们是你的试探工具
- Why? - We were a trial balloon.
你想要审查你的网站
You wanted to censor your sites,
如果我们失败了  你能说我们才是问题
but if we failed, you could point to us as the problem:
自由派非裔美国人律所
a liberal African- American firm.
-是吗  -所以我们才在这里  先生
- Really? - That's why we're here, sir,
让你面上好看
to make you look good.
很好  谢谢
Okay, good. Thanks.
我在海外还有些问题
Um, I, uh, I have a few issues overseas.
你们有时间吗  艾德里安  芭芭拉
Do you have a minute, Adrian, Barbara?
-有  -很好
- We do. - Good.
需要我做什么吗
Do you need anything from me?
不用了  我们就行  谢谢
No, I think we're good. Thanks.
你在干什么
What are you doing...
我要跟你谈谈
I need a second.
什么事
What?
你近期没有要升职合伙人吧
You're not up for partner anytime soon, are you?
没  据我所知没有
No, not that I know of.
你最好...
You should, uh...
跟你们律所从经济上撇清关系
stay clear of your firm's finances.
为什么
Why?
雷迪克&博斯曼从一个客户手上收了80万贿赂
Reddick/Boseman took an $800,000 bribe from a client.
可能会惹麻烦上身
It might be in trouble.
我不想让你惹上麻烦
I don't want you to get in trouble.
那个客户叫特拉维斯·利奥波德
The client's name is Travis Leopold.
好的
Okay.
谢谢
Thanks.